{
  "Q1": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 1,
      "Question": "How many hours are there in a day?",
      "Option A": "12",
      "Option B": "18",
      "Option C": "36",
      "Option D": "24",
      "Correct Answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 1,
      "Question": "Which of the following animals is not found in the sea?",
      "Option A": "Whale",
      "Option B": "Shark",
      "Option C": "Dog",
      "Option D": "Dolphin",
      "Correct Answer": "Dog"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 1,
      "Question": "Cold brew, latte, espresso are all examples of which beverage?",
      "Option A": "Tea",
      "Option B": "Coffee",
      "Option C": "Fruit Juice",
      "Option D": "Smoothie",
      "Correct Answer": "Coffee"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 1,
      "Question": "How many cents do 10 dollars make?",
      "Option A": "1000",
      "Option B": "100",
      "Option C": "10000",
      "Option D": "10",
      "Correct Answer": "1000"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 1,
      "Question": "A VIP is a known as a \"very what person\"?",
      "Option A": "Intelligent",
      "Option B": "Insecure",
      "Option C": "Important",
      "Option D": "Ideal",
      "Correct Answer": "Important"
    }
  ],
  "Q2": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 2,
      "Question": "In the world of video games, who has a brother called Luigi?",
      "Option A": "Wario",
      "Option B": "Mario",
      "Option C": "Yoshi",
      "Option D": "Toad",
      "Correct Answer": "Mario"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 2,
      "Question": "A London Landmark is known as what Ben?",
      "Option A": "Small",
      "Option B": "Large",
      "Option C": "Big",
      "Option D": "Medium",
      "Correct Answer": "Big"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 2,
      "Question": "A magnet would most likely attract which of the following?",
      "Option A": "Metal",
      "Option B": "Plastic",
      "Option C": "Wood",
      "Option D": "Glass",
      "Correct Answer": "Metal"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 2,
      "Question": "Which of these is a song by BTS?",
      "Option A": "Milk",
      "Option B": "Butter",
      "Option C": "Sugar",
      "Option D": "Honey",
      "Correct Answer": "Butter"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 2,
      "Question": "Which city is home to the Colosseum?",
      "Option A": "Barcelona",
      "Option B": "Madrid",
      "Option C": "Rome",
      "Option D": "Prague",
      "Correct Answer": "Rome"
    }
  ],
  "Q3": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 3,
      "Question": "How many wickets need to fall to dismiss a whole cricket team?",
      "Option A": "9",
      "Option B": "11",
      "Option C": "1",
      "Option D": "10",
      "Correct Answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 3,
      "Question": "What makeup product makes eyelashes appear longer?",
      "Option A": "Blush",
      "Option B": "Lipstick",
      "Option C": "Mascara",
      "Option D": "Foundation",
      "Correct Answer": "Mascara"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 3,
      "Question": "Complete the phrase, \"love of\" what \"is the root of all evil\"?",
      "Option A": "Power",
      "Option B": "Food",
      "Option C": "Money",
      "Option D": "Human",
      "Correct Answer": "Money"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 3,
      "Question": "Which animal is not a type of primate?",
      "Option A": "Gorilla",
      "Option B": "Lemur",
      "Option C": "Orangutan",
      "Option D": "Sloth",
      "Correct Answer": "Sloth"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 3,
      "Question": "Which of the following is not a type of Pasta?",
      "Option A": "Fusili",
      "Option B": "Pesto",
      "Option C": "Penne",
      "Option D": "Fettuccine",
      "Correct Answer": "Pesto"
    }
  ],
  "Q4": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 4,
      "Question": "What kind of edge denotes the forefront of innovation?",
      "Option A": "Sharp",
      "Option B": "Breaking",
      "Option C": "Cutting",
      "Option D": "Splitting",
      "Correct Answer": "Cutting"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 4,
      "Question": "When inhaled, which of the following gases makes voices sound higher?",
      "Option A": "Helium",
      "Option B": "Nitrogen",
      "Option C": "Argon",
      "Option D": "Sulfur Hexafluoride",
      "Correct Answer": "Helium"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 4,
      "Question": "Which instrument does not have strings?",
      "Option A": "Bass",
      "Option B": "Trombone",
      "Option C": "Guitar",
      "Option D": "Cello",
      "Correct Answer": "Trombone"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 4,
      "Question": "What is the first name of McDonald's mascot?",
      "Option A": "Donald",
      "Option B": "George",
      "Option C": "Ronald",
      "Option D": "Jim",
      "Correct Answer": "Ronald"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 4,
      "Question": "In terms of computing, what does the term GPU stand for?",
      "Option A": "Graphics powering unit",
      "Option B": "Graph preparing unit",
      "Option C": "Graphics performing unit",
      "Option D": "Graphics processing unit",
      "Correct Answer": "Graphics processing unit"
    }
  ],
  "Q5": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 5,
      "Question": "Which of the following are the reason a blood cell is coloured red?",
      "Option A": "Hemoglobin",
      "Option B": "Platelets",
      "Option C": "Oxygen",
      "Option D": "Insulin",
      "Correct Answer": "Hemoglobin"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 5,
      "Question": "The Olympic Games have been hosted the most by which country?",
      "Option A": "France",
      "Option B": "Canada",
      "Option C": "Japan",
      "Option D": "United States",
      "Correct Answer": "United States"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 5,
      "Question": "Which of the following provides protection for the teeth?",
      "Option A": "Gums",
      "Option B": "Crown",
      "Option C": "Enamel",
      "Option D": "Incisor",
      "Correct Answer": "Enamel"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 5,
      "Question": "The functions sine, cosine, and tangent correspond to which branch of mathematics?",
      "Option A": "Number theory",
      "Option B": "Algebra",
      "Option C": "Calculus",
      "Option D": "Trigonometry",
      "Correct Answer": "Trigonometry"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 5,
      "Question": "Which car company makes the Cayenne, Macan and Panamera?",
      "Option A": "Jaguar",
      "Option B": "Lexus",
      "Option C": "Porsche",
      "Option D": "Audi",
      "Correct Answer": "Porsche"
    }
  ],
  "Q6": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 6,
      "Question": "In which of the following countries was ice cream invented?",
      "Option A": "United States",
      "Option B": "China",
      "Option C": "Switzerland",
      "Option D": "England",
      "Correct Answer": "China"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 6,
      "Question": "Someone, who collects coins is called what?",
      "Option A": "Collector",
      "Option B": "Accumulator",
      "Option C": "Philatelist",
      "Option D": "Numismatist",
      "Correct Answer": "Numismatist"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 6,
      "Question": "The Hunger Games was written by which author?",
      "Option A": "Suzanne Collins",
      "Option B": "JK Rowling",
      "Option C": "Hannah Rothschild",
      "Option D": "Zadie Smith",
      "Correct Answer": "Suzanne Collins"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 6,
      "Question": "How many elements are there in the periodic table?",
      "Option A": "111",
      "Option B": "97",
      "Option C": "118",
      "Option D": "143",
      "Correct Answer": "118"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 6,
      "Question": "Which of these is a palindrome?",
      "Option A": "Clap of thunder",
      "Option B": "Nurses run",
      "Option C": "A rolling stop",
      "Option D": "Heavens to Betsey",
      "Correct Answer": "Nurses run"
    }
  ],
  "Q7": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 7,
      "Question": "Which game includes the phrase “Do not pass go, do not collect $200”?",
      "Option A": "Scrabble",
      "Option B": "Jenga",
      "Option C": "The Game of Life",
      "Option D": "Monopoly",
      "Correct Answer": "Monopoly"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 7,
      "Question": "How many hearts does an octopus have?",
      "Option A": "2",
      "Option B": "5",
      "Option C": "3",
      "Option D": "1",
      "Correct Answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 7,
      "Question": "The shape of which chocolate bar is intended to suggest the peaks of Swiss mountains?",
      "Option A": "Twix ",
      "Option B": "Kit Kat",
      "Option C": "Toblerone",
      "Option D": "Skor",
      "Correct Answer": "Toblerone"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 7,
      "Question": "Dump, floater, and wipe are terms used in which sport?",
      "Option A": "Water Polo",
      "Option B": "Volleyball",
      "Option C": "Curling",
      "Option D": "Tennis",
      "Correct Answer": "Volleyball"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 7,
      "Question": "What is the largest organ in the body?",
      "Option A": "Heart",
      "Option B": "Liver",
      "Option C": "Stomach",
      "Option D": "Skin",
      "Correct Answer": "Skin"
    }
  ],
  "Q8": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 8,
      "Question": "Who designed the Sydney Opera House?",
      "Option A": "Louis Kahn",
      "Option B": "Jorn Utzon",
      "Option C": "Walter Gropius",
      "Option D": "Richard Neutra",
      "Correct Answer": "Jorn Utzon"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 8,
      "Question": "In which Shakespeare play is jealousy called \"the green-eyed monster\"?",
      "Option A": "Hamlet",
      "Option B": "Macbeth",
      "Option C": "Othello",
      "Option D": "The Tempest",
      "Correct Answer": "Othello"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 8,
      "Question": "The founders of YouTube worked for which company before starting up YouTube?",
      "Option A": "IBM",
      "Option B": "PayPal",
      "Option C": "Microsoft",
      "Option D": "Google",
      "Correct Answer": "PayPal"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 8,
      "Question": "Which of the following is the smallest country in the world?",
      "Option A": "Nauru",
      "Option B": "Monaco",
      "Option C": "Malta",
      "Option D": "Vatican City",
      "Correct Answer": "Vatican City"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 8,
      "Question": "Which of the following musicians was not a member of the Beatles?",
      "Option A": "John Lennon",
      "Option B": "Ringo Star",
      "Option C": "Paul McCartney",
      "Option D": "Mick Jagger",
      "Correct Answer": "Mick Jagger"
    }
  ],
  "Q9": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 9,
      "Question": "What lies at the centre of a heliocentric model of the solar system?",
      "Option A": "Sun",
      "Option B": "Moon",
      "Option C": "Earth",
      "Option D": "Mars",
      "Correct Answer": "Sun"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 9,
      "Question": "Which character is voiced by Brad Pitt in the 2010 comedy animated film Megamind?",
      "Option A": "Hal Stewart",
      "Option B": "Metro Man",
      "Option C": "Megamind",
      "Option D": "Minion",
      "Correct Answer": "Metro Man"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 9,
      "Question": "Which Israeli coastal city shares its name with a type of biscuit?",
      "Option A": "Gaza",
      "Option B": "Haifa",
      "Option C": "Ashdod",
      "Option D": "Jaffa",
      "Correct Answer": "Jaffa"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 9,
      "Question": "Which of the following men does not have a chemical element named after him?",
      "Option A": "Niels Bohr",
      "Option B": "Isaac Newton",
      "Option C": "Enrico Fermi",
      "Option D": "Albert Einstein",
      "Correct Answer": "Isaac Newton"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 9,
      "Question": "The national flag of which country does not feature three horizontal stripes?",
      "Option A": "Russia",
      "Option B": "Germany",
      "Option C": "Hungary",
      "Option D": "Romania",
      "Correct Answer": "Romania"
    }
  ],
  "Q10": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 10,
      "Question": "Which fast food restaurant chain piloted a chicken-flavoured nail polish?",
      "Option A": "Popeyes",
      "Option B": "KFC",
      "Option C": "Mary Brown's",
      "Option D": "Chick-Fil-A",
      "Correct Answer": "KFC"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 10,
      "Question": "Who was the first woman to fly solo across the Atlantic?",
      "Option A": "Sally Ride",
      "Option B": "Amy Johnson",
      "Option C": "Elinor Smith",
      "Option D": "Amelia Earhart",
      "Correct Answer": "Amelia Earhart"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 10,
      "Question": "In the children's book series, where is Paddington Bear originally from?",
      "Option A": "Latvia",
      "Option B": "Peru",
      "Option C": "Colombia",
      "Option D": "India",
      "Correct Answer": "Peru"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 10,
      "Question": "Each read and outlined in white, there are how many stars on the New Zealand Flag?",
      "Option A": "1",
      "Option B": "4",
      "Option C": "6",
      "Option D": "3",
      "Correct Answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 10,
      "Question": "Eglantine is a species of which plant?",
      "Option A": "Ivy",
      "Option B": "Hollyhock",
      "Option C": "Iris",
      "Option D": "Rose",
      "Correct Answer": "Rose"
    }
  ],
  "Q11": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 11,
      "Question": "On which day of the week did Apple CEO Steve Jobs unveil the first iPhone?",
      "Option A": "Monday",
      "Option B": "Tuesday",
      "Option C": "Thursday",
      "Option D": "Friday",
      "Correct Answer": "Friday"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 11,
      "Question": "Three Hollywood actors who have starred as Magneto, Iron Man and Doctor Strange have all played what other character?",
      "Option A": "Captain Kirk",
      "Option B": "James Bond",
      "Option C": "Sherlock Holmes",
      "Option D": "Harry Potter",
      "Correct Answer": "Sherlock Holmes"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 11,
      "Question": "What is the title of the twelfth film in the James Bond series?",
      "Option A": "For Your Eyes Only",
      "Option B": "Moonraker",
      "Option C": "A View To Kill",
      "Option D": "The Spy Who Loved Me",
      "Correct Answer": "For Your Eyes Only"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 11,
      "Question": "What scientist first determined that human sight results from images projected onto the retina?",
      "Option A": "Copernicus",
      "Option B": "Galileo",
      "Option C": "Aristotle",
      "Option D": "Johannes Kepler",
      "Correct Answer": "Johannes Kepler"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 11,
      "Question": "The world's tallest building Burj Khalifa, consists of how many floors?",
      "Option A": "141",
      "Option B": "163",
      "Option C": "157",
      "Option D": "179",
      "Correct Answer": "163"
    }
  ],
  "Q12": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 12,
      "Question": "What was the first handheld game console to ship with a colour display?",
      "Option A": "Sega Game Gear",
      "Option B": "Gameboy Color",
      "Option C": "Atari Lynx",
      "Option D": "Neo Geo Pocket Color",
      "Correct Answer": "Atari Lynx"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 12,
      "Question": "Until now, which country has been the only FIFA World Cup host not to make it out of the group stage?",
      "Option A": "United States",
      "Option B": "Russia",
      "Option C": "Japan",
      "Option D": "South Africa",
      "Correct Answer": "South Africa"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 12,
      "Question": "After which Greek goddess is the US space program to land the first woman and the next man on the moon by 2024 named?",
      "Option A": "Rhea",
      "Option B": "Aphrodite",
      "Option C": "Artemis",
      "Option D": "Nemesis",
      "Correct Answer": "Artemis"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 12,
      "Question": "Which Scottish poet's works inspired the book titles \"Of Mice and Men\" and \"Catcher in the Rye\"?",
      "Option A": "James Hogg",
      "Option B": "Robert Burns",
      "Option C": "Robert Louis Stevenson",
      "Option D": "Walter Alva Scott",
      "Correct Answer": "Robert Burns"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 12,
      "Question": "Relative to the others, which planet spins backward?",
      "Option A": "Saturn",
      "Option B": "Mercury",
      "Option C": "Venus",
      "Option D": "Neptune",
      "Correct Answer": "Venus"
    }
  ],
  "Q13": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 13,
      "Question": "What Indian mausoleum was called a \"teardrop… on the cheek of time\" by Nobel Prize in Literature laureate Rabindranath Tagore?",
      "Option A": "Tomb of Jahangir",
      "Option B": "Qutub Minar",
      "Option C": "The Taj Mahal",
      "Option D": "Tomb of Cyrus",
      "Correct Answer": "The Taj Mahal"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 13,
      "Question": "Which Icelandic geothermal site has the same name as a 1980 movie?",
      "Option A": "The Shining",
      "Option B": "Xanadu",
      "Option C": "The Blue Lagoon",
      "Option D": "Heaven's Gate",
      "Correct Answer": "The Blue Lagoon"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 13,
      "Question": "Which Roman emperor preceded Nero?",
      "Option A": "Titus",
      "Option B": "Claudius",
      "Option C": "Tiberius",
      "Option D": "Augustus",
      "Correct Answer": "Claudius"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 13,
      "Question": "Wood hyacinth is another name for which flower?",
      "Option A": "Speedwell",
      "Option B": "Cyclamen",
      "Option C": "Primrose",
      "Option D": "Bluebell",
      "Correct Answer": "Bluebell"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 13,
      "Question": "The Earth is approximately how many miles away from the Sun?",
      "Option A": "39 million",
      "Option B": "193 million",
      "Option C": "93 million",
      "Option D": "9.3 million",
      "Correct Answer": "93 million"
    }
  ],
  "Q14": [
    {
      "Question Number ": 14,
      "Question": "Which king was married to Eleanor of Aquitaine?",
      "Option A": "Richard I",
      "Option B": "Henry II",
      "Option C": "Henry V",
      "Option D": "Henry I",
      "Correct Answer": "Henry II"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 14,
      "Question": "Which of the following landlocked countries is entirely contained within another country?",
      "Option A": "Burkina Faso",
      "Option B": "Mongolia",
      "Option C": "Lesotho",
      "Option D": "Luxembourg",
      "Correct Answer": "Burkina Faso"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 14,
      "Question": "\"Nephelococcygia\" is the practice of doing what?",
      "Option A": "Breaking glass with your voice",
      "Option B": "Sleeping with your eyes open",
      "Option C": "Sleeping in freezing water",
      "Option D": "Finding shapes in clouds",
      "Correct Answer": "Finding shapes in clouds"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 14,
      "Question": "Which scientific unit is named after an Italian nobleman?",
      "Option A": "Ohm",
      "Option B": "Volt",
      "Option C": "Pascal",
      "Option D": "Hertz",
      "Correct Answer": "Volt"
    },
    {
      "Question Number ": 14,
      "Question": "If you planted the seeds of \"Quercus robur,\" what would grow?",
      "Option A": "Trees",
      "Option B": "Grain",
      "Option C": "Flowers",
      "Option D": "Vegetables",
      "Correct Answer": "Trees"
    }
  ]
}